凛さの空調リエキス
He smells like sand!
一人で僕のとつが気になかった
深くnentめ
恋に薄かった
波そうすぐ
心が騒ぐよ
潰さない通りを
僕は欲を
君ら
I-I gratefully accept anyone's name!
Yes, I've put in a heartbeat!
I want to succeed, love-san!
I would like to succeed, Sashiko-san!
This is your promotion movie we filmed the other day.
No! No! I can't believe my weight!
So disappointing! Just two more centimeters!
I just wanted to lose two more centimeters!
I'm afraid it's already been broadcast throughout space via the web.
But now I'll be known as the idol without a waste throughout outer space!
Listen up!
It's nearly time to present the 77th generation to the public.
You will all be participating in various Handshake events.
We're debuting at a Handshake event?
That's right!
For AKB-0048, Handshake events are important places.
You get to interact directly with your audience and hear their honest opinions.
It's an excellent opportunity!
That's right!
Takamina-san!
You, Kirin-san!
Sayaka!
Good morning!
We're idols who go to see our audience.
We're also idols you can interact with.
The way you handle the Handshake event will dramatically affect your popularity going forward!
The best way to master this chance is with a heartfelt and powerful Handshake!
Then look directly into their eyes and smile!
It's very important to acknowledge each and every one of your fans!
Acknowledge?
It means remembering their names, faces, what you talked about, and anything else!
Amazing!
Finally, you'll be wearing plain clothes.
Huh?
Handshake events are the only place we are able to wear plain clothes and show off our personal styles.
This is an important element which will determine if your fans will like you or be disappointed.
What?
I had no idea clothes were so important!
What am I going to do?
The only proper clothes I have is my school uniform!
Do you want to borrow mine?
You can borrow some of mine if you'd like!
Oh, really?
Don't bother!
Huh?
Takamina and Yurkarin are the twin towers of plain clothes!
What?
What did you say?
I can't believe you said that!
Plain clothes, huh?
Our lessons start this afternoon!
Uh-huh!
Ready, and...
Let's go!
AKB 0048!
Thank you very much.
僕は語ろう名も無き詩人のように熱く
君が涙に触れているなら慰めよりもやがて白む空を語ろうか
次回予告
Hey! Have you changed yet?
Oh, I do like that!
Ta-da!
I just don't know what to do anymore!
My weight is fried! It's fried!
This cost 30,000?
I only have 2,000!
We can't even buy this!
We ended up not buying anything!
Nagisa! Whatever you do, don't wear your school uniform!
But why not?
The mail's here!
Look at this!
There's a fan letter for Orine!
I love it!
Oh, I'm so envious!
Already? That's amazing, Orine!
How can that be? I haven't even debuted yet!
Well, maybe they saw that trainee promotional video and they're investing in you early, Orine!
Oh, it's not a letter, it's data!
Let's play it back with my phone!
Yeah!
Orine Aida!
You confused, foolish, and ugly pig!
Shoshiko requires your special ability to turn the worthless into the greatest, and losers into winners, something you couldn't do!
You are timid and disgusting!
Your dancing is terrible and has no spirit!
You don't have what it takes to be a professional!
Claiming you'll succeed...
Let's stop this!
Um...
Take it off!
Orine Aida!
You are a pathetic and hideous stain on the history of my beloved Zero Zero!
Quit Zero Zero by the next Handshake event!
If you don't, I'll blow up the venue and end your Zero Zero life!
What do you think you're watching?
Tsubasa-san!
You know you're only allowed to accept fan letters we've examined first!
I didn't think these would come yet. We didn't check them close enough.
Oh, Orine...
It's nothing to worry about. We get these kinds of letters all the time.
But...
The previous Sashiko graduated just two years ago. She was very popular.
The more popular and visible a member is, the more haters she'll have as well.
The same goes for members who look up to them.
Uh...haters?
If this is all it takes to break you, you won't be able to keep going.
But it's a criminal threat!
A group like AKB-0048 that fights against the DES can't shrink from criminal threats?
You must try to be resolute. A single hater will sadden many fans affecting others' happiness.
We cannot allow that to happen.
Come, it's time.
Go to the lesson room.
Okay.
Come on, come on, come on! You move like bisons! Put your hips into it more!
Okay!
Your dancing is terrible and has no spirit. You don't have what it takes to be a professional.
Ugh!
What are you spacing out for, Orune?
Uh...I'm sorry!
Enough already!
Huh?
I can't believe you're shaken by that. Do you honestly think you can really be a successor like that?
Cherry, you don't have to put it like that! Gosh, don't be so mean!
You don't have to put it like that!
What are you spacing out for, Orune?
Uh...I'm sorry!
Enough already!
Huh?
I can't believe you're shaken by that!
Do you honestly think you can really be a successor like that?
Cherry, you don't have to put it like that! Gosh, don't be so mean!
Orine!
Oh, come on!
Wait! Orine!
Why would you say that? You saw the video, Cherry! Think about it! No one would be able to brush that off!
It's troubling!
I'm sorry!
Enough already!
Huh?
I can't believe you're shaken by that!
Do you honestly think you can really be a successor like that?
Cherry, you don't have to put it like that! Gosh, don't be so mean!
Orine!
Oh, come on!
Wait! Orine!
Why would you say that?
You saw the video, Cherry!
Think about it!
No one would be able to brush that off!
It's troubling!
I don't want her to give up over something like that!
Otherwise, my dream will never come true!
Her dream? Our dream?
Hey, are you talking about—
I suppose I have no choice.
I'll go bring her back. You girls keep practicing!
Okay!
Cheery.
I'm at my limit!
Hey, what's wrong? Are you okay?
Orine! What's wrong?
Here.
Thank you.
Everyone has haters.
Even you have them?
Yeah.
Being Zero Zero's captain is my responsibility as Takamina. I used to get tons of people saying I was unreliable, lack the right aura. There are still people like that.
Why would they say such mean things?
Do you really think it's mean?
What?
Oh, right! I came to do my business! I passed my limit!
Ah!
No, no, no, no!
Ahhh!
You and Yuka, my dear friends.
The women at the factory were nice to me too.
But somewhere inside, I still felt no one would look at me.
That's awful.
I wanted someone to look at me.
But I...
I never knew having people look at you could be so terrifying.
It's okay, though.
I'll participate in the Handshake event.
I'll be brave.
Even Takamina-san said everyone is haters.
It's part of becoming a member of Zero Zero.
Orine.
Handshakes originally had individual and national events.
But Zero Zero Handshake events combined both of these formats,
which is why they're held in a stadium.
There's a ton of people!
There are lanes!
It's starting.
Your handshaking starts at 1350, ladies.
You'll take over the lanes of members going on break in the afternoon.
The 77th generation will go into two lanes as groups of four and three.
I'm so nervous.
Once you've changed, you'll wait until it's time.
Got it? Yes!
Sonata, you're wearing that?
I'm wearing bunny ears today!
You're wearing your uniform?
Well, you know, at least it's nice and neat.
Well, that's not the biggest problem.
Why are you dressed like that? Are you taking this seriously?
You should all know by now that I'm never not serious.
What?
Is it so she won't be taken back, huh?
Oh, come on.
I'll let you borrow my clothes, so put these on.
Here.
I don't think you need to force it.
I think this look is nice and boyish, you know?
Whoa!
It's a...
Thanks so much.
Huh?
I'm sorry!
Orine, are you okay?
Orine?
It's almost time to go, girls.
Orine, can you do it?
Yes.
We'll all be right here to protect you, Orine!
The Buddha will protect you too!
The Buddha will prove to be an excellent assistant for me!
Don't call me your assistant!
Thank you.
Everyone.
There's no one here.
I know it's only natural, but it's still rough.
Excuse me, are you Orine Aida?
Yes, ma'am.
When she saw your promotional video, my little girl just couldn't stop talking about how cute you were.
She's dying to meet you.
She's Orine's fan?
That's amazing!
Come on, Yayoi.
Ask her to shake your hand.
Would you please...
Shake my hand?
Orine?
Come on, you can do it.
Yeah.
My first handshake.
Come on, you need to say thank you to her like a big girl.
Thank you!
Huh?
Thank you so much!
I'm so happy!
Why aren't you crying too?
Be good!
Bye-bye!
Thank you!
See you later!
Bye-bye!
Thank you!
See you later!
Bye-bye!
It's you!
I told you not to come!
Chiri!
What are you doing?
doing nice to meet you i'm 77th generation trainee chieri sono thank you for coming today it's really
nice to don't tell me you actually it wasn't me you won't get away with it get him wait what
let's not catch him or do anything like that don't you care what happens to the handshake event
he needs to pay for doing something so horrible to you but
they're here it's the des yes we've spotted several des drones and transport ships in the air
there's a strong possibility they're carrying paratroopers successors ensure the fans safety
trainees ambush them give them everything you have what do you want us to fight them by ourselves
that girl
we're in a heads up girls let's go okay
come on everyone let's protect our fans
draw them outside the venue okay got it
this area is dangerous don't push everyone wait your turn
are you all right stop stop you
are you hurt are you okay don't touch me i won't be fooled no matter how nice you act you are never
going to be sashiko i'll never accept it
sashiko was my everything
i won't let anyone else tarnish sashiko's name not you or anyone ever
that's it this boy's room
it was full of sashiko's products
sashiko's posters gravier images support journals this boy loves sashiko
he really really loved her
enemies incoming be careful
so
let me protect you please
because you're my first hater i want to cherish you
i like sashiko-san too i love her
please tell me i know i'm not her yet so please just tell me how to do it
what do i need to do to become the sashiko-san i love
what
let's go come with me
okay
let's go
so
It's the Woda.
Woda?
I've seen those clothes at concerts.
They're a group of hardcore, dedicated fans
who fight alongside us when things get really dangerous.
They fight with us?
Saisha!
Wodasan!
You're a tough one, aren't you?
Oine!
Kamina-senpai!
Please, take care of this boy!
No need to worry.
He'll be alright.
That's right.
Haters teach you what you're lacking.
Things you wouldn't notice behind your back.
If I'm not good at dancing,
I just need to practice more than anyone else.
If I'm timid,
I should hold my head high.
Haters may be scary,
but they're all so kind.
And stay away!
How'd you like that?
Oh, we're saved!
I'm so glad that everyone's alright!
Orine!
Miss!
You are so amazing!
If they release your cards,
I'll buy all of them!
Thank you!
Oho!
I knew it!
These machines…
What's that means?
Orane, you have mail.
What?
Shubasa-san!
We already checked it.
Orane Aida isn't suited to become Sashiko.
For starters, your fighting style is simply too weak.
Sashiko may have been sloppy, but she wasn't so weak.
Your lucky Woda was there.
If you had been alone, they would have captured you.
Sashiko can even use a handicap like long hair as a weapon.
But your conscientious attitude is similar, which is actually rare.
If you work hard, you might stand a slim chance some day.
Wait a minute! He's praising you!
My first hater.
It was terrifying.
But it was also a kind new experience.
My second hater.
This is all great.
Would you like to share my life with you every day as you've got a call?
ethicis
You've already met him.
If he contemptuous, he's the тамmer.
Thank you.
次の世代へ
夢はリンカーネーション
何度でもデジャビューのような
遠い記憶
まるでリンカーネーション
今もまた無意識のうちに
どこかへ走ってる
いくつ目の涙で
あきらめるのか
いくつ目の命で
かなうものなのか
ご視聴ありがとうございました